

Mohammad Ilyas Kohistani Full-Stack Web <u>Developer</u>

• MEVLANA MAH. YILDIRIM BEYAZIT CAD. ESENYURT, 37500 Istanbul, Turkey

💌 alyas.kohistani@gmail.com 📞 +905526966353 🎬 Mar 20, 1998 🏲 Afghan

in linkedin.com/in/mohammad-ilyas-kohistani-81b437129 😯 github.com/IlyasKohistani

Profile

passionate full-stack PHP web developer with over three years of experience developing web based applications. Developed a highly customize-able, risk assessment system focused on design modularity and code flexibility. Handled all steps of the development lifecycle; from requirements gathering/estimating to customer support and enhancements. Worked as part of a remote team utilizing an array of communications tools to ensure seamless results.

Professional Experience

IGW Organization, *Mobile developer* 2015 – present

IGW Organization, *Full-stack web developer* 2015 – present | Kabul, Afghanistan

AIESEC Organization, *Responsible for outgoing exchange and event manager* 2018 – 2019 | Kabul, Afghanistan

	Languages	
Persian		_
English		_
Turkish		_

Skills

PHP, Laravel, React, MySQL, jQuery, Ajax, Dart, Flutter, Android Studio, Javascript, ASP.NET, SASS, CSS, HTML5, Redux

Education

Kabul University,

Bachelor degree/ computer science 2016 – 2019

Ghulam Haidar Khan, *Degree of high school* 2015

Projects

SDROA ERP,

Mobile application for SDROA organization 2020

Available on Apple Store

ROBUSTA,

Robusta coffe house management system 2019

SDROA2.ORG

2017

As a UIUX designer

EventHub,

An easy event management mobile application.

Courses

React & Redux, *Udemy* 2020

Advanced CSS and Sass: Flexbox, Grid, Animations and More!, *Udemy* 2019

PHP with Laravel, *Udemy* 2016

Organisations

ALPHA, *Event manager* 2018 – present

AIESEC, responsible for outgoing exchanges 2017 – 2019 | Kabul, Afghanistan